
Microsoft (R) .NET Framework Strong Name Utility  Version 4.0.30319.0
Copyright (c) Microsoft Corporation.  All rights reserved.

Usage: sn [-q|-quiet] <option> [<parameters>]
 Options:
  -a identityPublicKeyFile identityKeyPairFile signaturePublicKeyFile
    Generate AssemblySignatureKeyAttribute data to migrate the identity key to the signature key from a file.
  -ac identityPublicKeyFile identityKeyPairContainer signaturePublicKeyFile
    Generate AssemblySignatureKeyAttribute data to migrate the identity key to the signature key from a key container.
  -c [<csp> [<provtype>] ] 
    Set/reset the name of the CSP to use for MSCORSN operations.
  -d <container>
    Delete key container named <container>.
  -dg <assembly> <digest file> [-rehash]
    Compute the digest of an assembly, generating a digest file for signing by
    the -ds or -dsc commands.
    If -rehash is specified, modules are re-hashed before digest calulation
  -ds <digest file> <keyfile> [-ecma]
    Sign a digest file generated by the -dg command using the full key pair
    from the given key file.
    If -ecma is used, keyfile is treated as the real key for ECMA signing.
  -dsc <digest file> <container> [-ecma]
    Sign a digest filegenerated by the -dg command using the key in the
    specified key container.
    If -ecma is used, container is treated as the real key for ECMA signing.
  -di <digest file> <assembly>
    Insert the signature from the digest file signed by the -ds or -dsc
    commands into the assembly.
  -dh <digest file> <hash file>
    Extract the base64 encoded hash value from the digest file
  -du <signature file> <digest file>
    Update the signature in the digest file with a base64 encoded signature
    in a signature file. WARNING: using this operation may result in a digest
    file that contains an invalid signature for its corresponding assembly.
  -dd <digest file>
    Dump the digest file to the console
  -D <assembly1> <assembly2>
    Verify <assembly1> and <assembly2> differ only by signature.
  -e <assembly> <outfile>
    Extract public key from <assembly> into <outfile>.
  -i <infile> <container>
    Install key pair from <infile> into a key container named <container>.
  -k [<keysize>] <outfile>
    Generate a new key pair of the specified size and write it into <outfile>.
  -m [y|n]
    Enable (y), disable (n) or check (no parameter) whether key containers
    are machine specific (rather than user specific).
  -o <infile> [<outfile>]
    Convert public key in <infile> to text file <outfile> with comma separated
    list of decimal byte values.
    If <outfile> is omitted, text is copied to clipboard instead.
  -p <infile> <outfile> [<hashalg>]
    Extract public key from key pair in <infile> and export to <outfile>,
    embedding the specified hash algorithm (sha1|sha256|sha384|sha512).
  -pc <container> <outfile> [<hashalg>]
    Extract public key from key pair in <container> and export to <outfile>,
    embedding the specified hash algorithm (sha1|sha256|sha384|sha512).
  -Pb [y|n]
    Enable (y), disable (n) or check (no parameters) the CLR policy allowing
    trusted applications to bypass strong name signature verification on their
    assemblies.
  -q
    Quiet mode. This option must be first on the command line and will suppress
    any output other than error messages.
  -R[a] <assembly> <infile> [-ecma]
    Re-sign signed or partially signed assembly with the key pair in <infile>.
    If -Ra is used, hashes are recomputed for all files in the assembly.
    If -ecma is used, infile is treated as the real key for ECMA signing.
  -Rc[a] <assembly> <container> [-ecma]
    Re-sign signed or partially signed assembly with the key pair in the key
    container named <container>.
    If -Rca is used, hashes are recomputed for all files in the assembly.
    If -ecma is used, container is treated as the real key for ECMA signing.
  -Rh <assembly>
    Re-compute hashes for all files in the assembly.
  -t[p] <infile>
    Display token for public key in <infile> (together with the public key
    itself if -tp is used).
  -T[p] <assembly>
    Display token for public key of <assembly> (together with the public key
    itself if -Tp is used).
  -TS <assembly> <infile>
    Test-sign signed or partially signed assembly with the key pair in 
    <infile>.
  -TSc <assembly> <container>
    Test-sign signed or partially signed assembly with the key pair in the key
    container named <container>.
  -v[f] <assembly> [{-ecmakey <keyfile> | -ecmacontainer <container>}]
    Verify <assembly> for strong name signature self consistency. If -vf is
    specified, force verification even if disabled in the registry.
    If -ecmakey is specified, keyfile is treated as the real ECMA key.
    If -ecmacontainer is specified, container is treated as the real ECMA key.
  -Vk <regfile> <assembly> [<userlist>] [<testkey>]
    Generate a registry script in <regfile> to register <assembly> for
    verification skipping (with an optional, comma separated list of usernames
    for which this will take effect and an optional test public key in
    <testkey>). <assembly> can be specified as * to indicate all assemblies or
    *,<public key token> to indicate that all assemblies with the given public
    key token. Public key tokens should be specified as a string of hex digits.
  -Vl
    List current settings for strong name verification on this machine.
  -Vr <assembly> [<userlist>] [<infile>]
    Register <assembly> for verification skipping (with an optional, comma
    separated list of usernames for which this will take effect and an
 optional test public key in <infile>).
 <assembly>    can be specified as * to indicate all assemblies or *,<public key token> to
    indicate that all assemblies with the given public key token. Public key
    tokens should be specified as a string of hex digits.
  -Vu <assembly>
    Unregister <assembly> for verification skipping. The same rules for
    <assembly> naming are followed as for -Vr.
  -Vx
    Remove all verification skipping entries.
  -?
  -h
    Displays this help text.
